- I don't know. Tell her I'm sick.
- Okay.
Not the kind that would make her
wanna take care of me.
(Leonard:)But nothing so critical that she'll feel
uncomfortable if I wanna try this again.
(Sheldon:)Got it. So I'm assuming nothing venereal.
(Sheldon:)I'll just tell her that you had
a routine colonoscopy...
(Sheldon:)...and haven't quite bounced back.
- Give me the phone.
- I thought you wanted to cancel.
I can't. If I don't show up,
she'll still be expecting you.
(Sheldon:)Why would she be expecting me?
(Leonard:)Stop asking me all these questions.
I need to take another shower.
(Penny:)- Are the rest of the guys meeting us here?
- Oh, yeah.
(Leonard:)No.
(Leonard:)Turns out that Raj and Howard
had to work...
(Leonard:)...and Sheldon had a colonoscopy,
and he hasn't quite bounced back yet.
(Penny:)Ooh, my uncle just had
a colonoscopy.
(Leonard:)You're kidding. Well, then,
that's something we have in common.
(Penny:)How?